export default [
    {
        question: "What is the virtual DOM in React?",
        answers: [
            "A browser feature that React uses for performance optimization.",
            "A lightweight representation of the actual DOM in memory.",
            "A special type of DOM used for virtual reality applications.",
            "An experimental feature for rendering React components."
        ],
        correct: 1
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "What is the main purpose of React Router?",
        answers: [
            "To manage the state of React components.",
            "To create animations in React applications.",
            "To handle routing and navigation in single-page applications.",
            "To organize the folder structure of a React project."
        ],
        correct: 2
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "In React, what is the significance of the 'key' prop when rendering a list of elements?",
        answers: [
            "It specifies the color of the elements.",
            "It is used to uniquely identify elements when rendering lists.",
            "It sets the font size for the list items.",
            "It determines the position of the elements on the screen."
        ],
        correct: 1
    }
    ,    

    {
        question: 'JSX is typesafe?',
        answers: [
            'True',
            'False',
            'None of the Above',
            'Cannot Be Determined'
        ],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'React merges the object you provide into the current state using which of the following',
        answers: [
            'setState()',
            'State()', 
            'getState()', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 1
    }, 
    {
        question: "What lifecycle method is used for performing side effects in a React component?",
        answers: [
            "componentWillUnmount",
            "componentWillUpdate",
            "componentDidMount",
            "componentDidUpdate"
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
       
    {
        question: 'Arbitrary inputs of components are called?',
        answers: [
            'Keys',
            'Props', 
            'Elements', 
            'Ref'
        ],    
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'useState' hook in React?",
        answers: [
            "To manage component routing.",
            "To fetch data from an API.",
            "To manage and update state in functional components.",
            "To style components using CSS."
        ],
        correct: 2
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "What is a controlled component in React?",
        answers: [
            "A component that is uncontrollable and cannot be manipulated.",
            "A component that manages its own state internally.",
            "A component that relies on external state management.",
            "A component that is restricted from rendering in certain contexts."
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'map' function in React when rendering lists of elements?",
        answers: [
            "To apply a function to each element in an array and return a new array.",
            "To sort the elements in the list.",
            "To filter out certain elements from the list.",
            "To reverse the order of the elements."
        ],
        correct: 1  
    }
    ,{
        question: "What is React context used for?",
        answers: [
            "Styling components with CSS.",
            "Sharing data between components without explicitly passing it through props.",
            "Managing routing and navigation.",
            "Creating animations in React applications."
        ],
        correct: 1
    }
        ,
    
    {
        question: '_____ can be done while more than one element needs to be returned from a component?',
        answers: [
            'Abstraction',
            'Packing', 
            'Insulation', 
            'Wrapping'
        ],    
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following needs to be updated to achieve dynamic UI updates?',
        answers: [
            'State',
            'Props', 
            'Components', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Lifecycle methods are mainly used _____',
        answers: [
            'To keep track of event history',
            'To enhance components', 
            'Free up resources', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 3
    }
]